Vikentor Pierre

Florida, Orlando
(561) 318-9898
www.modevtech.com
vikentorpierre@gmail.com

ABOUT

Experienced full-stack web-developer of 4+ yrs. Am knowledgeable in creating rich modern UI/UX design, debugging, and deploying backend Api solutions. Able to work independently, as well as in a team. For my full portfolio visit www.modevtech.com

EXPERIENCE

Derive System, Orlando -- Product QA/QC

10/ 2018 - PRESENT

An auto-mobile software company that makes and sells car tuners. We have three stack web, mobile app, and device firmware.

Vespo, Orlando -- Web/los junior developer

10/ 2018 - 07/2019

A start-up app that helps small businesses to connect with customers, and reward customers for shopping with them.

Mosdevv, Orlando lead Web/los developer

10/ 2015 - PRESENT

Mosdevv is a small business I have with my friend. We make websites and apps for our clients.

EDUCATION

Palm Beach State College, (PBSC)

AA Computer Science(CS)

University of Central Florida(UCF)

Currently, On my last two semesters.

To obtain my BS In Computer Science(CS)

SKILLS

Languages

- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- IOS/Swift
- AJAX
- jQuery
- Git

Framework

- React.js
- Vue.js
- Django
- Material.ui
- Bootstrap

More

- Express.js
 - API
- Node.jsPostgres
- MongoDB
- Deploy
- Hosting
- UI/UX
- Figma
- O., .
- ScriptingGitHub
- SEOAgile

INTERESTS

- Data science
- Learning French/Spanish
- Al/ Machine learning
- Decentralize application